VICTOR COELHO







Data engineer with more than 7 years of experience in the technology field. Also experience in marketing include brandina, performance, social media and media out of home. Some highligehted soft-skills are organization, creativity, fast-paced learning, problem-solving, commnunication, and innovation.

Skill

- Python | SQL | DBT | GIT | PySpark | Spark | BigQuery | Airflow | Databricks | OOP | API Rest | Fast API
- · Docker | Flask | AWS | Oracle | Data lake | Data Warehouse | Pandas | GO | Docker Composer
- · GCP | Postgres | NoSQL | Kanban | Data Lakehouse | SOLID | Clean Code | Microservices | Terraform | CI/CD
- · GA4 | MongoDB | GTM | Pandas | DuckDB | SQLAlchemy | Node.JS | API | DDD | Kafka | Datadog | Nginx

Work Experience _____

Senior Data Engineer II [02/2024 unit | now]

- · Working as a senior data engineering consultant in Brazilian big companies such as Grupo OLX (OLX, Zap Imóveis and Viva Real) and RD Saúde (RaiaDrogasil and DrogaRaia) and Implementation and migration to GA4:
- Working on building the architecture and implementation of the cloud using GCP (Google Cloud Platform) for companies' data democratization strategy and decision-making support;
- Construction and implementation of data collection maps on websites using GTM and on Android and IOS apps with Firebase SDK for Google Analytics:
- Construction and maintenance of the Data Warehouse, performing data modeling (Star schema, SnowFlake and Data Vout) and ETL processes.

Stack Tec. -

Senior Data Engineer [10/2023 - 02/2024]

- · Structure provisioning (Virtual machines, postgres instances, loadbalancer) as code using Terrafoform;
- · Data Lake development using GCS, Parquet and Delta;
- · Development of pipelines using Python, Spark and SQL. Within them using technologies such as: Cloud function, Dataproc, Datatransfer;
- DataWarehouse development and data modeling using Dataform and DBT;
- · Development of crawlers using selenium, webdriver, docker and Cloud Run;
- · Development of pipelines using Mage.ia (Google Ads, Amazon Ads, Google Ad Manager, Active Campaign);
- Webscraping the public and private site's for ingest in data lake (Google Cloud Storage).

Burger King

Senior Analytics Engineer [11/2022 - 10/2023]

- · Data Lake team with the creation and support of data pipelines (API's and WebHooks)
- Data mapping and automation of manual routines and processes
- Development of fact, dimension and aggregate tables for Data Warehouse
- Development of the conversion and revenue attribution algorithm for campaigns and communications.
- · Development and management of the RR panel (Results meeting VP Technology)
- Development and management of the C360 panel CIA's general panel for monitoring general KPIS on sales, customers, app users.

Education _

Bachelor degree Software Engineering [2019 - 2023]

Bachelor technology degree Marketing [2019 - 2020]